ILGWU David Dubinsky Foundation Records 5780/104
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 1971 Awards. Mail Ballot (Box 8, Folder 15)
  Correspondence and copies of mail ballots.
- 1971 Awards. Minutes of the Fifth Meeting (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Summary of the meeting along with copies of the schedule of awards.
- 1971 Awards. National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing (Box 8, Folder 17)
  Appeal to the foundation and a proposal to support the Legal Services Department.
- 1971 Awards. National Farm Workers Service Center (Box 8, Folder 18)
  Appeal to the foundation and a proposal for funding of the Rodrigo Terronez Memorial Clinic
- 1971 Awards. Progress Reports [Part 1 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 19)
  Annual reports from award recipients on how grant money is being used.
- 1971 Awards. Progress Reports [Part 2 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 20)
- 1971 Awards. Recipients (Box 8, Folder 21)
- 1971 Awards. Rejects [Part 1 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 22)
  Rejection letters
- 1971 Awards. Rejects [Part 2 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 23)
- 1971 Awards. Requests (Box 8, Folder 24)
  List of organizations requesting grants and notes about them.
- 1971 Awards. Taxation with Representation (Box 8, Folder 25)
- 1971 Awards. United Federation of Teachers (Box 8, Folder 26)
- 1971 Awards. University of Wisconsin-Madison. Industrial Relations Research Institute (Box 8, Folder 27)
  Requesting for grant renewal and report of how previous grants were used.
- 1971 Awards. Workers Defense League (Box 8, Folder 28)
  Regarding the WDL's publication and an appeal to the foundation.